<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>I Just Do Things</title>
    <link>https://ijustdothings.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on I Just Do Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 13:04:43 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ijustdothings.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Graphics with Pi Pico and SSD1306 OLED Display</title>
      <link>https://ijustdothings.com/posts/pi-pico-oled-experiments-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 13:04:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ijustdothings.com/posts/pi-pico-oled-experiments-1/</guid>
      <description>A photo of the Pi Pico held together by gaffer tape
  Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been diving into the world of simple graphic elements and finding ways to render them on a compact SSD1306, similar to those I&amp;rsquo;ve used in other projects like SpaceHex - Github.
In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the development process of a modular display-based tool using the RP2040 Pi Pico and an SSD1306 OLED display with Micropython.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of Anthony: A Singular Ant-Man Tale</title>
      <link>https://ijustdothings.com/posts/singular-ant-man-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 10:31:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ijustdothings.com/posts/singular-ant-man-tale/</guid>
      <description>The Legend of Anthony
  Hey folks, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a crazy story to tell you today. Over the past couple of years, I&amp;rsquo;ve had this thing happen to me about a dozen times where I find a singular ant just hanging out on my arm or leg. It&amp;rsquo;s happened at home, at work, even in the middle of the city. Weird, right?
Anyway, someone recently called me an animal summoning Disney princess because of this, and it got me thinking&amp;hellip; what if this ant is my own personal superhero, like Batman or Ant-Man?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Blog, Who Dis?</title>
      <link>https://ijustdothings.com/posts/new-blog-who-dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ijustdothings.com/posts/new-blog-who-dis/</guid>
      <description>New Blog, Who Dis?  Link to heading   It&amp;rsquo;s a question that we&amp;rsquo;ve all asked at some point in our lives - whether we&amp;rsquo;re starting a new job, moving to a new city, or embarking on a new adventure. And it&amp;rsquo;s a question that I&amp;rsquo;m asking myself today, as I sit down to write my first post for this brand new blog.
My name is Nathaniel Evry, and I&amp;rsquo;m a passionate technologist with a diverse set of skills and a love for innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ijustdothings.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ijustdothings.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me  Link to heading   Greetings! I&amp;rsquo;m Nathaniel Evry, a passionate technologist with a diverse set of skills and a love for innovation. With years of experience in the tech industry, I&amp;rsquo;ve built and implemented software systems for a variety of clients and projects. Currently, I serve as the Chief Research Officer at quub, a small aerospace startup. In this role, I bring my knowledge of miniaturized electronics, signal transmission and reception, hardware design, coding, architecture, and research to the table.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
